[music]
I didn't [music] know
Uh-huh.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Come on.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
[music]
Well, good evening. [laughter]
It's all good. We'll try again. Welcome.
We're trying something new. Did y'all
like it? Was it fun?
>> Yes. Well, welcome to Movement Church.
[music]
Miracle and healing night. Are you
excited?
All right. Come on. Let's [music] forget
about our day. Let's worship the Lord
tonight. Okay. Here we go.
Come on. Put your [music] hands like
this. I'm shaking off the heaviness.
I'm dancing out of [music and singing]
my regrets.
I'm throwing caution to the wind.
No, I am not [music and singing] ashamed
to praise.
Some say it's foolishness,
but I say it's worth the risk.
I can't forget what Jesus
[music and singing] did.
No, I am not ashamed to praise. [music]
I
Where [singing] are those chains I want?
[music]
I'm free. I'm free. I'm free. I'm free.
[music and singing] My sin is gone. How
can it be? I'm free. I'm [music] free.
I'm free. [singing]
free. Look at what the Lord has done.
[music] I'm never going back [singing]
to the way I was. I sing of dance
[music] cuz I really I'm free. [singing]
I'm free. Thank God [music] I'm free.
[singing]
[music]
I've got a friend that never quits
or no one [music and singing] love as
good as this.
And I don't care what anyone says.
[singing and music]
I'll never be ashamed to praise like
[music and singing] this. There are
those days where
I'm free. I'm free. [music and singing]
I'm free. I'm free. My s
I'm free. [singing and music] I'm free.
on the living with the Lord. [singing]
I am never going back to the way I was.
I sing I sing [music and singing] of I
God. I'm [music and singing] free. Lord,
you took the cross and you broke your
body. [music]
You shed your blood. Now [singing] the
sinner can't see. My dead is [music]
laid and my record is clean. I couldn't
do it, so you did it for me. You took
the [music] cross [singing] and you
broke your body.
You shed your blood, now the sin against
[music] my debt is paid and my [singing]
record is
I couldn't do it, [music] so you didn't
cross. You took the cross and you
shing
[music]
[singing]
out. Where are [singing] those chains
that won't tell me? I'm free. I'm
[music] free. I'm free. I'm free. My sin
[singing] is gone now.
I'm free. [music] I'm free. I'm free.
I'm free.
What the Lord has. [singing] I am never
going back to the way [music] I will
sing. Sing [singing]
it. I [music]
free. I'm free.
>> [singing]
>> God, I'm free. But you took the cross
and you [music] broke your body.
You shed your blood, now the [singing]
sinner can't.
My dead [music] is paid and my record is
I couldn't [singing] do it, so you did
it to us. You took the cross and you
[music] Heat. Heat. Heat. [singing]
[music]
[singing]
I do. So [music and singing] you did it
for the only
[music]
Heat. Heat. Heat.
I'm never going back to the way.
Look at what [music and singing] the
Lord has done. I'm never going back to
the way I [music]
look at what the Lord has done. I'm
never [music] going back to the way I
[singing] was. I praise that you're free
because he set you free. Amen.
>> AMEN.
>> AMEN. [cheering]
>> ALL RIGHT. ARE you ready to really
praise tonight? Here we go. Say
>> allelujah.
>> Ready?
>> Yeah.
>> Here we go.
>> Hallelujah.
You get all the praise. We say
hallelujah.
You get all the praise. is
hallelujah. [music and singing]
You get all the praise. We say
[music and singing] hallelujah.
[music]
You're
>> doing good. Come on. Get a [singing]
little bounce in your step.
[music] Halle hallelujah.
You get [singing] all the praise. We say
hallelujah.
[music]
You get all the praise always. [singing]
And I've got a God who is for. [music]
Oh, he's known for making way.
He fought the [music and singing] battle
so I wouldn't have to. All glory belongs
to his name.
I've got a God who's been faith.
Oh, [music] far more than I could have
slayed.
Through every season, in spite of all my
weakness, he gave me a song I can sing.
I came to praise. [music] I declare that
tonight.
>> I came to praise.
>> That's why I woke up today.
>> That's [music] why I woke up today.
[singing]
>> I came to praise.
So [music]
we say hallelujah.
[music]
You get all the praises we say. Amen.
Amen. [music and singing] Hallelujah.
You get all the praise away. [music]
And I got a king who is risen.
Oh, he put my [music] shame in the
grave.
To hell and back. And now I [singing]
never have to. And he did it all in
three days. I came [music] to praise.
I came to praise.
>> That's why I woke up today.
>> That's why I [music] woke up today.
>> I came to praise.
So we say [music] halle
[singing] Hallelujah.
You get all the praise. We say
hallelujah. [music]
[singing]
You get all the praise.
>> [music]
>> I see the one [singing]
I'm seeing.
I see [music] the battle. That's how I
fight. I see it's holy. [music]
I see it twice. I see it's holy.
[singing] The rest of my
[music]
night. I see the battle. That's how I
fight. I [music] see holy
twice.
Holy [music]
the rest of my life
the rest of [music and singing] my life.
Hallelujah. [music] You get all the
praise. We got everybody.
Halle Hallelujah. [music]
Get all the praise. You always [singing]
[music]
Hallelujah.
We get all the praises we say halle
[music]
[singing]
hallelujah.
We get all the praises away. I'm singing
morning [music and singing]
sing
[music]
the rest of my life. [music] Hallel
[singing]
Hallelujah
to give all [music] the praise.
Come on, sing it out. [music]
>> I came to praise.
>> I came to praise. [music] Get out of my
way.
>> Out of my way.
>> I came to praise.
>> Hallelujah. Come on, let's praise the
[cheering] LORD TONIGHT. OH, WE THANK
YOU, FATHER. COME ON, lift your hands
and worship him tonight. It doesn't
matter what you're going through. It
doesn't matter what battle you're
facing. We worship the Lord because we
know we have the victory.
>> For mine,
nailed to the cross, you crucified
all my [music and singing] sin and
shame. It was washed by your mercy.
You [music] are the treasure [singing] I
find,
reason for living. [music and singing]
So let my life become an offering
to the one who is worthy.
Come on, let's sing it out.
All praise [music]
[singing] to the Lord most high.
All praise to the one
[singing and music] who saved my life.
All praise to Jesus Christ, high king
[music and singing] of heaven,
my king forever.
>> Stor [singing]
the gates of my heart.
The veil [music] in between was torn
apart. Now you hold [music] the keys to
the grave. Come on church, let's sing
this. [singing] Great things to life.
And you roll stones away.
[music]
>> All [singing] praise to the Lord most
high.
All praise to the one
[music and singing] who saved my life.
All praise to Jesus Christ, high king
[music] of heaven, my king [singing]
forever.
All praise to the Lord
[singing and music] most high.
All praise to the one who saved my life.
All praise [music and singing]
to Jesus Christ, my king of heaven,
[music and singing]
my king forever.
You're my king forever.
We worship you, Jesus.
Lift my hands [music]
and worship you. We worship [singing]
you.
I lift [music and singing] my hands up.
Lay my whole life down. My [singing]
whole life down is for you.
I [music and singing] lift my hands up,
lay my whole life down. My whole
[singing] life down [music] is for you.
And I lift my hands [music and singing]
up, lay my whole life down. My whole
life down [music]
is for [singing] you.
I lift my hands up, lay my whole life
down. [music] Cuz my [singing] whole
life down is for you.
And I lift [music and singing] my hands
up, lay my whole life down. My whole
[music and singing] life down is for
you.
I [singing] lift my hands up, lay my
whole life down. My whole
[music and singing] life now is for you.
All praise to the [music] Lord most
high.
All praise [music] to the one who
[singing] saved my life. All praise to
Jesus [music]
[singing] Christ,
my king of heaven, my king
[music and singing] forever.
All praise to the Lord most [singing]
high.
All praise to the one [music] who saved
my life. [singing] All praise to Jesus
Christ,
my king [music] of heaven, [singing]
my king forever. I lift [music] my hands
up. My [singing] whole life I
[music]
down is for [singing] you.
I lift my hands up. My [music] whole
life down. My whole [singing] life now
is for you.
[music]
All praise [singing]
to the Lord most high
and all praise [singing and music] to
the one who saved my life. All praise to
Jesus Christ,
my king [singing] of heaven, [music]
my king forever.
All praise [music] to the Lord most
[singing] high.
All praise to the one who saves my life.
[music]
All praise to Jesus [singing]
Christ, high king of heaven, my king
forever.
>> Come on, let's [music] lift our hands
[singing] and worship the Lord.
You are [singing]
my king. [music]
You are my king, [music and singing]
Lord.
Oh, [singing]
we bless [music] your name. Oh, we give
you praise.
You are the same
each and every [music and singing] day.
So, we bless your name,
Lord. We give you praise.
You are the same
every day.
We worship you, Jesus.
We thank you, Father.
We bless your name, Jesus. You're such a
good and a faithful God.
We welcome you in this place tonight.
[music]
>> [singing]
>> I
simple melodies [singing] of sacrifice.
Open hands and open [music and singing]
hearts. You're the only one I want.
Treasure my [singing] delight.
like
Holy [music] Spirit [singing] fall
like gra
Holy [music and singing] Spirit have
your way.
Let [singing] your glory fall down. Let
your glory fall [music] down.
thing I ask, I seek so
[music and singing] much more than
anything to dwell within your house for
all [music and singing] my days.
Lord, knowing you is [music and singing]
everything. So I let go of lesser
things. You alone are [singing] worthy
[music] of my praise.
So stir in [singing] me a passion for
your name.
All [singing]
I pray
Holy [music]
Spirit fall
I pray.
Holy [music and singing] Spirit have
your way.
Let your glory [singing and music] fall
down. Let your glory fall down.
Fall. [singing]
[music]
Holy Spirit. Fall. [music and singing]
Holy [music and singing] Spirit. Have
your way.
Let [singing] your glory [music]
fall down. Let your glory [singing] fall
[music] down.
Have your way. Have your [music] way.
[singing]
May I never lose the wonder
of your [singing] presence. [music]
May I always stand in awe of who you
are.
Oh, the beauty and [music] the gift
of your friendship
is unlike anything
I've ever known. [music and singing] May
I never
May I never lose the water [singing]
of the [music] resence.
We always stand and [singing] above who
you are. [music]
Oh, the [singing] beauty and the gift
[music]
of the over
like [music]
anything
I've ever known so far.
[music and singing]
Oh, Holy Spirit. Holy [music] Spirit
fall [singing]
away. Holy Spirit
[music] of you. [singing]
Let your [music] glory fall down. Let
your [singing] glory fall.
[music]
Oh
my. [singing]
Holy Spirit [music] pour
come and have your way.
Have you
[music and singing]
let your glory forever
[music]
lose the wonder [music]
of [singing] your words?
[singing]
All the beautiful [music]
gift
[music and singing]
your gra
[music]
[singing] your presence
I always stand
of who you
of the beauty and the [music] gift
of [singing] your presence
unlike anything [music]
I've ever known.
All [music and singing]
I pray,
Holy [singing]
Spirit,
I pray,
Holy [singing] Spirit, [music]
have
your way.
Let [singing] your glory [music] fall
down. Let your glory fall down.
Let it fall.
>> [music and singing]
>> Let it fall. [singing]
Come on, let's lift our hands and we
[music] press into [singing]
his presence. Oh, we turn our attention
to you, Jesus. [music]
May we never forget. [singing] May we
never forget.
You are the one true living God. [music]
Oh, we bless your name. [music]
We bless your name.
>> Praise your name.
>> We bless [singing] your name.
We bless your name. [music]
>> [singing]
>> like rain.
Come on, church. Let's just press in for
just another minute. [music] Just lift
your hands, lift your [singing] voices.
Oh, we thank you, Lord.
[singing]
>> [music]
[music]
>> We praise you.
[singing]
[music]
Oh,
we bless your name.
We give you praise. [singing and music]
We thank you, Father.
>> Thank you, Jesus.
>> We thank you, Jes.
>> Oh, let's just lift up our hands right
now and thank him. Let's just thank him
for being a good God. Thank him for his
glory. Thank him for his goodness. Thank
him for his power.
Thank him for the fact that you're here
tonight. [music]
>> That he's kept you your entire life.
>> Thank you, Lord,
>> that we live in this amazing country
where we can worship you freely.
Oh, thank you, [music] Lord. Thank you,
Lord.
Thank you, Lord.
You know, there's just nothing like
being in the presence of God. There's
just nothing like it. There's nothing
comparable.
You know, when Moses went up on that
mountain, I I I think I mentioned this a
few Sundays ago. Moses went up on Mount
Si and he got the Ten Commandments.
And the Bible says that he was up there
a long time. And when he came down, he
was literally glowing in the glory of
God. They could see something was
different about Moses. It was like his
entire countenance had changed. It was
different. Let me tell you, you can't be
in God's presence and stay the way you
are. Can you imagine being on that
mountain with God?
Just you and him. Just you and him
having a conversation. But you know, you
can have that same relationship. Matter
of fact, you can have a better
relationship because that same God who
was up on that mountain with Moses 40
days and 40 nights, that same God who
was speaking to Moses, writing the Ten
Commandments out with his finger on
tablets of stone. That same God dwells
on the inside of you. That same God
wants to have a relationship with you
and I.
He's a personable God. And in the Old
Testament, he wasn't able to have as
close a relationship as he wanted. But
now, there's nothing that can block it.
There's nothing that can hinder. There's
no sin. There's no problem. There's no
shame. Nothing. And once you're born
again, he comes to live on the inside of
you. And he can have a close, intimate
relationship with you if you want it.
It's not up to God.
Hey, it's not up to God if you read your
Bible. It's not up to God if you spend
time praying. Does God want you to do
these things? Absolutely.
But just like you do in a marriage
relationship with or with a boyfriend or
a girlfriend, the more time you spend
with them, the more your relationship
begins to develop. What about the less
time you spend? Well, you don't know him
that well, right? This is one of the
biggest problems we have as Christians.
We don't know God very well. And he's a
God that's not a far off. He's a God
that's close and the Bible says he
inhabits the praises of his people. He
loves it when we do what we just did
tonight and worship him. But you know,
you don't have to wait for a church
service to worship God. You can worship
him in your car. You can worship him in
the shower. That's when you'll sing the
best. You'll be you'll be in the shower
worshiping God thinking, "Man, I should
try out for the worship team." And then
you get out and your your wife is like,
"No, you shouldn't cry out for the
worship team." There's something about
the acoustics of that,
you sound better than you do. Amen. You
can worship him anywhere.
God loves it when we worship him. He's
done so much for us. The least we can do
is give him thanks. The least we can do
is worship him. Amen. Amen. Praise God.
Well, [music] you guys can be seated
tonight. Is anybody excited to be here
tonight? Healing and miracle night at
Movement Church. We got any hungry
people in the room tonight? Any hungry
people in the room? I'm not talking
about physically hungry. You may not
have eaten supper yet, but I'm talking
about being hungry for the word. I know
if you're here on a Wednesday night,
you're hungry for the word. Amen. I want
to share with you just for a few
minutes, and then we're going to pray
for some people, lay hands on some
people. But I want to share with you
just for a few minutes some things that
the Lord has been dealing with me. Some
things the Lord has been putting on my
heart. Um and and there's a lot Thank
you. a lot of things to do with healing.
But let me just say this. I I've shared
this before, but uh several months ago I
had some Jehovah's No, it wasn't
Jehovah's Witness. It was uh Mormons
come to the front door of our house. I
got to spend some quality time really
talking with them and sharing Jesus with
them and and all of that. And you know,
it was real interesting. I really had a
revelation that day. I was really asking
the Lord because I really wanted to help
them. I really wanted to minister to
them. And I I I reached a point where I
saw that there was nothing else that
could be done. There was nothing else
that could be said. There was nothing
else I could do to convince them that
that what they were doing wasn't aligned
with scripture. And that wasn't
scripture over there, by the way. That
little other book you're holding is not
scripture. That's not the word of God.
And I and I and I just had a revelation
and I was just like, "We've reached an
impath, right? They don't believe the
Bible. I don't believe the Book of
Mormon. How are we ever going to resolve
this?" And the Lord and I and I as we as
I left and and they left and and they
finally just, you know, broke away from
me. The the and they put us on a list.
Haley was telling me that she they
approached her the other day and and
said she goes to movement church and
they they bolted really fast. [laughter]
So, I guess we're a blacklisted now,
maybe. Amen. But anyway, I was I was
just praying about it like, Lord, how
can we ever reach them? Because it's not
a logical argument that we can we can
make. And the Lord began to talk to me
about the power of the Holy Spirit and
began to talk to me about how this is
why you need miracles in your life. This
is why you need the power of God in your
life. Because yeah, you can argue all
day about f uh the concepts of the word
and different scriptures, but nobody can
argue with the power of God. When the
power of God is present, when the power
of God manifests, you just can't argue
with it. Somebody was sick and now
they're healed. Somebody was missing
something in their life and now it's
fixed. Somebody was broken and now
they're no longer broken. When the
manifested power and presence of God
shows up, it changes their life and it
will change the way they think. Amen.
>> Christians need the power. I refuse to
be without the power of God. I refuse to
do what I do as a pastor without the
power of God. If I don't have the
supernatural power, I don't want to do
anything. I don't want to preach. I
don't want to lay hands on people. I
don't want to do anything. It's not just
a philosophical argument that we make.
It's not just words on a page. These
words are full of power.
>> You and I are full of power. So tonight,
what I want to share with you is is what
this power is, where it comes from, and
I I want to share a little bit about how
we receive this healing and when we can
have it. 2 Corinthians chapter 5:E1 17,
it says, "Therefore, as any if anyone is
in Christ, he is a new creation. Old
things have passed away. Behold, all
things have become new. What I want you
to see tonight and focus on is the fact
that salvation begins as soon as you're
born again.
Salvation begins as soon as you accept
Jesus as your savior. Why am I saying
this? I'm saying this because there are
many Christians and there's a popular
thought process that that when you get
born again, the ultimate goal is for you
to go to heaven.
And being saved is all about going to
heaven. Now, let me tell you, go
heaven's an amazing place. We're going
there. Okay? Heaven's an amazing place.
We're going there. All of our loved ones
that are born again before us are there
waiting for us. It will be bigger and
awesome, if that's a word, than you've
ever dreamed. Okay? I am not minimizing
at all going to heaven. I look forward
one day to going to heaven in about 50
years.
I'm serious. I'm planning on being here
at least 100 years. Amen. If you don't
start amening maybe 99. No, I'm kidding.
But heaven's going to be an awesome
place. But you don't have to wait till
you get to heaven to experience
salvation.
Amen.
You don't have to wait till you get to
heaven to experience the blessings of
salvation because salvation begins now
when you're born again now. Amen. Let me
ask you, are you saved tonight?
>> Okay. So, so you're already saved.
Salvation begins now. And the benefits
of your salvation begin now. You know,
when you go to work for somebody, you go
to work for a company, when do the
benefits start? As soon as you sign and
say, "I'm a part of this company. I
signed my name. I'm now part of this
company. I'm going to go to work for
you." The benefits start immediately,
right? They should start immediately
depending on the company, but you you
should have uh benefits associated with
you as being a part of that company. God
is not different. He's not making you
wait 40, 50 years for you to have
benefits. Yes, one day we're going to
heaven, but salvation is for today.
And salvation is a big word. It is a
multiaceted word. The the Greek word is
sooo. That's the root word for
salvation. And it means being made whole
in your spirit, soul, and body.
Restored to health. Let me just read it
to you. The definition here. Restored to
health to deliver, to rescue you from
danger, to make you whole, and to heal
you. So, it's really not a question
whether or not healing is a part of
salvation. It's in the definition. Now,
some people will even argue with that,
right? They'll be like, "Well, I don't
know if healing is for today. I don't
know if healing is a part of salvation."
The definition says it is. And this is
not just a random de uh this is right
out of Strong's concordance, one of the
most popular, well-defined uh
concordance it that's ever been made.
Strong's concordance says that salvation
so includes healing. So it's not really
a question. Not too many people, some
will, but not too many people will
question whether healing is for you. The
question is where is that healing?
Where do I find that healing? Yeah, God
heals people when he sends them to
heaven. A lot of people believe that and
they'll say, "Yeah, healing is available
and one day we'll be healed when we get
to heaven." Let me tell you something
that is not true
for the one. Amen.
It's not. Let me tell you something.
When just just ask ourselves a question,
okay? When people approached Jesus and
they needed healing in their body, how
did Jesus respond? Did Jesus would they
come up to Jesus and then they're a
leopard and say, "I know you can heal
me, but I don't know if you will." And
Jesus says, "I will." He draws a sword.
Just hang on a second. Whack.
Going to heaven and you'll be healed.
Oh, you need healing in your body? All
right. Well, hang on. I'm going to push
some horrible disease and sickness on
you so in two months you'll be dead and
then you'll be healed.
But that's exactly what many people
believe. Many people believe that you'll
get healed when you're in heaven. Let me
tell you tonight, there's nothing to be
healed from in heaven. There's nothing
to be healed from. There's no sickness
there. Of course, there's no You're
healed in heaven because there's no
sickness in heaven to be healed from.
When when you leave your body one day,
what happens to your body? Your body is
here on this earth that you don't take
it with you. It's we put it in the
ground and we have a memorial service
for you. Your body STAYS HERE. YOUR BODY
MUST not have gotten healed if it was a
sickness or disease that took you out.
Well, they're healed in heaven, but
their body's still here and their body
didn't get healed. You see the
difference? But I'm here to tell you
tonight that salvation includes healing.
And you don't have to wait till you get
to heaven to experience salvation and
all the benefits of it because healing
is available today. Amen.
>> So, where does this healing come from?
How how is it that we have healing on
this earth today? Well, let's read this
out of Luke chapter 4 verse number 18
says, "The spirit of the Lord is upon me
because he has anointed me to preach the
gospel to the poor. He has sent me to
heal the brokenhearted, to proclaim
liberty to the captives and recovery of
sight to the blind, to set at liberty
those who are oppressed." So Jesus said
this. Jesus said, "The spirit of the
Lord is upon me. He's anointed me." Now
let's ask OURSELVES A QUESTION. WHY DOES
JESUS NEED TO BE ANOINTED?
Why does he need to be anointed? I mean,
is Jesus, Most people believe, this is
another popular belief in Christian
circles, that Jesus healed because he
was Jesus. Well, he was Jesus, so he
could heal people. No, he couldn't. He
couldn't heal anybody until he was
anointed by the Holy Spirit.
And once he was anointed by the Holy
Spirit, he proclaimed it. He found, the
Bible says, he opened the the scroll of
Isaiah and he found the place where it
was written. Ah, there I am. The spirit
of the Lord is upon me. He has anointed
me. What has he anointed me to do? He
anointed me to preach the gospel to the
poor. He's anointed me to heal the
brokenhearted, set at liberty though the
to the captives, recovery of sight to
the blind. He's anointed me to do this.
I am anointed to do this. How is healing
happening now on the earth? Because
there's an anointed man going around
healing everybody. There's a man who's
been anointed by the Holy Spirit healing
everybody. And everywhere he went, he's
healing people. And he wasn't healing
them by killing them so he could send
them to heaven.
Come on, somebody. He wasn't hurt. He
wasn't putting sickness on them so he
could heal them. That's another one
people say, "Well, you know, God God
tears you down so he can bring you up."
No, he doesn't.
If he did, show me scripture where Jesus
did that. Show me scripture where I'm
gonna come to Jesus and he's like,
"Okay, I I'm gonna tear you down so I
can lift you up. I'm g I'm gonna break
you snap in two and I'm gonna make you
broken and miserable so you have to come
to me and you have to worship me."
That's not true.
If it were true, there would be
scripture supporting that idea. But I'm
here to tell you, so many people believe
that. So many people believe that God's
going to break you. God's got to he's
got to break you down and and just break
you down so he can lift you back up.
That's not the God we serve. Jesus
wasn't anointed to hurt you. He was
anointed to heal you. And that
anointing, he said, "The spirit of the
Lord is upon me. He has anointed me."
Jesus was anointed by the Holy Spirit.
And guess what? You and I are anointed
by the same Holy Spirit.
You and I have the same Holy Spirit. And
you and I, if you've been baptized in
the Holy Spirit, are anointed with the
same Holy Spirit because Jesus said when
he ascended unto heaven, the last thing
he said to his disciples, do you think
this was important?
I mean, if someone was going to go away
for a long period of time and they were
going to be gone for uh couple thousand
years and but yet they're going to tell
you something before they leave, what
they're going to tell you. How many you
know that they weren't just talking
about the food they ate. That was good
pizza last night. Yeah, good pizza.
Yeah, it was great. Great restaurant.
All right, we'll see y'all later. Couple
thousand years. We'll see you later. No,
he was talking about very, very
important things. And in Acts chapter
one, we get a glimpse. We get we get
from Jesus mouth himself how this
healing is going to take place now that
he's leaving now that he's leaving this
earth. Acts chapter 1 verse8 he said but
you shall receive power when the Holy
Spirit has come upon you. So Jesus said
the spirit of the Lord is upon me. He
has anointed me. But now he's talking
about the Holy Spirit coming upon you.
Now there are two different things here.
You've got the Holy Spirit on the inside
of you when you're born again. You've
got an anointing on the inside of you.
The spirit of God lives on the inside of
you. These people were born again.
But now he's talking about another
experience with the Holy Spirit where
literally you can be baptized in the
Holy Spirit and have the Holy Spirit not
just living on the inside of you but
covering all over you. And the Bible
says that the Holy Spirit ascended or
descended from heaven and it looked like
fire coming from heaven and the fire
came down on each one of them and they
were all baptized in the Holy Spirit.
They began to speak with other tongues.
You lose a lot of people when you
mention that. I don't know why. I I
think it's because the devil has fought
so hard to stop you from operating under
the anointing. He's fought so hard to
prevent Christians from taking that next
step that God wants you to take. BECAUSE
LET ME TELL YOU, HE wants you walking
around this earth just like Jesus did.
He wants you walking around healing
people. He wants you walking around
laying hands on people. Is that not what
he told us to do?
That that's why the devil has fought
this so hard is because he's oh, we get
hung up on the tongue thing. Stop
getting hung up on the tongue thing.
Yes, you get to speak in the heavenly
prayer language and that's awesome. But
you forget what Jesus said. YOU'RE GOING
TO GET POWER WHEN YOU DO. And this power
we know is dunamis power. This is God's
miracle working power. So what we're
saying is when you're anointed by the
Holy Spirit and this power comes on you
now you are the ones that are to take
healing and deliverance and open blind
eyes and set captives free to all the
earth.
>> Jesus is not going to be here physically
walking the earth anymore. It's on us
now. It's on you and I. We're the next
ones. And the question for for for year
after year after this for for for
century after century is who's going to
step up?
Who's going to step up? Who's going to
actually believe what Jesus said? Now,
you'll find a lot of theologians that
will completely cut this up and and try
to explain away why this is not for
today. You'll have a lot of people try
to explain away why this power is not
for today. And we just wish God would.
We hope he would. So then they start
developing other doctrine which says he
breaks you and smacks you down because
and sometimes Jesus will heal you and
sometimes he won't. That's all a bunch
of hoie.
Why? Because they they don't embrace the
power of God. And when you don't have
the power of God, none of these other
things will even be possible. So we got
to explain them away.
But we're talking about how you can walk
in and operate in this power. Jesus said
that we could operate in this power and
be his witnesses in Jerusalem, Judea,
Samaria, and to the ends of the earth.
Like Salana, Texas, like McKini, like
Aubrey,
like Dallas. Wherever you go, you take
the power with you. Why? Because you're
anointed.
You've been anointed by God. You have
this power on you. Now, Paul had the
power. I won't get into all the
scriptures tonight, but you know,
there's there's been people over the
years, it's kind of funny. There's been
people over the years uh I want to do
exactly what Paul did and things like
that. And I remember one account in
scripture, they they were just taking
handkerchiefs, remember? And and Paul
was just putting his hands on them and
they would take these handkerchiefs that
Paul just put his hands on and they
would put them on people and those
people would be healed. Demons would
come at them because the handkerchief
got put on them. So I had someone come
to me one time said, "Pastor, we got to
get the handkerchiefs out.
We got to get the handkerchiefs out.
It's so easy to focus on the wrong
thing. It wasn't the hanky or the snot
that was on it. Can I just be real
blunt? Too late. I was
It wasn't the handkerchief. It was the
anointing
on the Apostle Paul's life. And that
anointing, listen to me, that anointing
can be transferred
from one to another.
That anointing is supposed to be
transferred from one person to another
person. It's supposed to. Remember when
Jesus was walking along? Famous story.
We talked about it so many times, but
it's good to hear it again. He's walking
along and the woman with issue of blood,
been sick for 12 years, comes up behind
Jesus and just touched the hem of his
garment. Didn't even touch his skin.
Touched the hem of his garment, the
cloth of his garment. And and the Bible
says that virtue better translation
would be power came out of him because
it was dunamis that said to come out of
him.
Power came out of him. Why? Jesus was
anointed and when she touched in faith
his garment, that anointing that was on
him flew out of him and into her. And
Jesus said he felt it happen. And that's
why he stopped. He could feel that
anointing going into somebody else. Oh,
praise God. We need to know about the
anointing. We need to operate under the
anointing. We need to embrace the
supernatural power of God and do exactly
what Jesus said. We've got a whole world
to reach, guys. We've got a whole world
that's dying and hurting. And they need
to see something besides religion. They
need to see something besides us just
quote scripture. They need to see
somebody walking on this earth that's
anointed. Remember when Jesus was in the
storm and the boat was sinking and he
got up and he rebuked the wind and the
waves AND THEY SAID, "WHAT KIND OF A MAN
IS THIS?" There's an answer to that
question. The answer to the question
that they asked, nobody answered it in
the Bible. It was just them. They're
like, "What kind of a man is this?" It
was a man anointed by the Holy Spirit.
And let me tell you something. There is
a man that pastors movement church
that's anointed by the Holy Spirit. But
guess what? I'm not the only one. It's
not just for pastors.
Praise God. It's for me, too. I'm
thankful. Well, you're just aware. No. I
I'm TELLING YOU TODAY THAT YOU ARE
anointed by the Holy Spirit. When the
when the Holy Spirit comes upon you and
you're baptized in the Holy Spirit,
YOU'RE ANOINTED AS WELL TO DO WHAT? THE
EXACT SAME thing that Jesus did. Because
what the anointing is on you. The
anointing does what it does. The Bible
says it removes burdens from people's
lives and it destroys yolks in their
life. We're not talking about egg yolk
now. We're talking about bondage that
the enemy has put on you. We're talking
about sickness and disease. We're
talking about anything that's happened
to you as a result of being on this
planet that God did not want to happen.
Let me tell you, the anointing will
break it. Amen. So, that anointing is on
us. This is how people get healed today.
It's because of the anointing. It's not
the handkerchief.
Ah, goodness. We get hung up on on that.
I'll show you another one we get hung up
on. Look at this one. James 5:14.
Is anyone among you sick? Let him call
on the doctor. No, no, no. That's not
what it says.
Boy, it gets quiet when I start picking
on this one, isn't it? Isn't that the
first thing most people do today? Born
again, spiritfilled, anointed of God
will call the doctor first. YOU SHOULD
CALL the elders of the church first and
say, "Pray with me right now that this
junk will leave my body." And you can
even do it. You can still go to the
doctor. I'm not, no one's mad at you for
going to the doctor. There's nothing
wrong with going to the doctor, but the
Bible says, I mean, believe what the
Bible says. The See, when we get this
out of here, here's the thing. Oh my
goodness.
Prayer and asking for prayer from the
leaders of the church should not be the
last resort. Well, we've done everything
else. We've done everything else we can.
I guess I'm going to go see if someone
can pray for me now.
You get the picture. That should be the
first thing that we do when something,
hey, agree with me in prayer. I know
this doesn't belong to me. I plan on go
seeing a doctor if I still have it next
week. But praise God, I know the
covenant promises I have in the word.
And when we agree together, we can
rebuke. And that anoint rebuke whatever
that is. And that anointing will remove
that burden from your life.
So many Christians will get healed first
before they even have to go to the
doctor. You'll save money. Oh, I got
your attention now, didn't I? You'll
save money. Amen.
So, it says, "If anybody is among you
sick," he's talking to the church.
Let him call for the elders of the
church and let them pray over him.
Listen to this. Anointing him with oil
in the name of the Lord.
Anointing them. Well, we are the
anointed ones and we are the ones doing
the anointing.
Did you catch that part? We are the
anointed ones now.
And we are the ones with the anointing
on us to anoint someone else with what?
The anointing.
What is that? It's the power. It's the
dunamis.
And the Bible says that when we do that,
that anointing that's on us, now here's
what's happened. Here's what's happened.
People get stuck on the oil. Well,
pastor, go get the vial of Where's the
vial of oil? Well, I got some oil. But
the anointing is not in the oil. It's
symbolic.
[laughter]
I think this is funny.
The anointing was It wasn't the hanky.
It wasn't the oil. It was the anointing
on it. It was the fact that we are
anointed. That's why the handkerchief
was anointed. It wasn't someone and had
someone, you know, they try to do all
these handkerchief things and dip them
in all kinds of spices and they smell
good and all. Okay, great. But that's
not going to get the job done. People
have over complicated this healing thing
so bad and they try to figure it out.
Oh, we just got to figure this out. HOW
DID PAUL DO THIS? HOW DID HE DO THIS?
What kind of hanky was it? Did it have
little frilly things on the side? Did he
use it before he handed it out and
prayed over it? Oh, praise God. No. Oh,
no. No. No. No. Please. No.
Was it even a handkerchief or was it
just a piece of cloth? What kind of
cloth was it? What color was it? See, we
get h we get hung up on all the wrong
thing. The point being is it was the
anointing transferred to that cloth. It
was the anointing flowing through Jesus
body into his clothes.
into that woman with the issue of blood.
It's the anointing right here flowing
from the elders of the church into
somebody. And look what the very next
verse says. And the prayer of faith will
so
save the sick and the Lord will raise
him up and if he has committed sins, he
will be forgiven.
Did you hear what I just read? And the
prayer of faith will save the sick. So
when we anoint someone with oil and we
pray the prayer of faith on them, what's
the Bible say it's going to happen?
It's not a trick question. The prayer of
faith will save the sick.
So he said, if you're sick, call on the
elders of the church. They will lay
their hands on you, anoint you with oil,
and they'll pray the prayer of faith on
you. Not the prayer of doubt and
unbelief over you. Not the prayer. Boy,
I hope this works. Well, I don't know
what kind what you say you had. Oh, have
you been to the doctor yet? Oh, I'm I'm
I'm pointing the finger at ministers,
too. How many ministers will first ask,
"Have you been to the doctor?" You know,
Jesus never asked that question.
Guy with leprosy, been full of leprosy.
Have you been to the doctor? What did he
say? How bad is it? How how many how
many weeks you got left to live?
Pressure, pressure, pressure. Why?
Because then you're looking at your own
strength and your own ability. Let me
tell you, none of those things matter.
Let me say it again. None of those
things matter.
The kind of sickness it is, how long
you've had it, none. Did it matter to
Jesus? Was he like, "Oh, no. How long
have you been sick? Oh, no. What do you
have?" None of those things mattered.
Why? Because the anointing
doesn't care.
The anointing is more powerful than
whatever it is that you got.
True. It's the anointing. It's the
anointing. It's the supernatural power.
That anointing that's on us is more
powerful than the sickness that's in
your body or the pain that you're
experiencing or whatever it is. The
anointing is more powerful. God's power
is greater than that.
And when you believe that and we pray
for you, the prayer of faith, that's
believing it. The Bible says the prayer
of faith will save the sick. That's
exactly what we're going to do tonight.
If anybody has sickness in their body
and you want us to pray for you, we're
going to do exactly what the Bible says.
We're going to I'm telling you right
now, my hands are anointed right now.
We're already anointed. Well, you're
gonna get the good oil from from Israel.
I'm serious, guys. People get so
not against the oil from Israel,
but don't get hung up on the oil or the
handkerchief or the method or it's the
anointing.
I said it's the anointing.
You and I are anointed. How How is this
healing going to take place on the earth
if there's no anointing here?
How would it ever take place? Jesus
said, "It's here. The spirit of the Lord
is upon me. He's anointed me to go do
everything that I'm doing." And you
know, Most Bible scholars believe he
prayed that prayer everywhere he went.
He would go in the synagogue and say the
spirit, that's how he started every
single service that he started in every
single city. The spirit of the Lord is
upon me. He has anointed me.
It was huge. It was big. He announced it
from the beginning. And I'm announcing
it tonight. The spirit of the Lord is
upon us. He has anointed us with what?
The same power that raises the dead. The
same power that cures cancer. The same
power that heals sickness and disease.
The same power
that'll cure any issue that you're
having tonight. Let me tell you
something. God wants every person here
tonight healed.
How do I know that? Because his word
says he desires that all men be saved
and come to the knowledge of him. And
that word saved is the word so.
That means not just salvation going to
heaven. It means healing. And it starts
now. I said it starts now. It starts
right now. If you have sickness in your
body, I want you to come forward right
now. If you got pain in your body, if
you're having any kind of physical
problems, mental problems, thank you,
Lord.
Thank you, Lord, for the anointing.
Let's just be praying right now,
listening to the Holy Spirit. Let's
listen to his voice.
Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Jesus.
Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Lord.
What can we pray with you?
Ringing.
Yeah. Acting up.
Well, the devil's getting on your
nerves. That's what I just heard. So,
we're going to get the devil off your
nerves in the name of Jesus and the
anointing that's on our life. We declare
right now, nerves, you function
properly. Devil, you get off her nerves
right now in Jesus name. Nerves, you
function properly in the name of Jesus.
Will not have this. She's a child of the
king. We pray and agree right now. the
prayer of faith, believing, trusting
you, Lord, as the healer. And that
anointing right now is flowing into her
body, healing what's been broken, uh,
putting together, what's been
disconnected. Thank you, Lord, that she
does not have to have this the rest of
her life. I don't care what others have
said. The answer is no. God says, "No,
you don't have to have this. The world
says you do." The world says, "Oh, it's
just a part of Bell's policy. Oh, it's
just a part of this." But you've been
redeemed from the curse of the law. That
doesn't apply to you.
Thank you, Lord, for healing right now
in the name of Jesus. Every nerve, every
nerve functioning properly in the name
of Jesus. Thank you, Father. Yes, ma'am.
Oh, put your hand right there on her
chest. In the name of Jesus, we rebuke
that crud. We pray the prayer of faith
over her right now. Healing, wholeness
over her lungs, clear lungs in the name
of Jesus Christ of Nazareth. Thank you,
Lord, for that anointing right now
flowing into her body. The spirit of the
Lord is upon us. We are anointed for
this purpose to lay hands on the sick.
And the sick, you have no choice. You
have to recover in the name of Jesus.
Lungs, you have to be clear right now in
Jesus name. Oh, just take a deep breath.
Take a deep breath. Thank you, Lord, for
clear lungs in the name of Jesus. Thank
you, Lord. Thank you, Lord. Clear lungs
in the name of I'm glad you came forward
because the Lord told me to pray for you
tonight. You weren't coming forward. I
was calling you out, girl. Thank you,
Lord.
Yes. Yes. Thank you, Lord. Thank you,
Lord. Lay your hands on her back.
Father, in the name of Jesus,
we come into agreement right now. Thank
you, Lord, for the anointing. Thank you,
Lord, for the anointing. Oh, the spirit
of the Lord is upon us. We are anointed.
You got a bunch of anointed hands laying
on you right now. Back, you line up in
Jesus name. Body, you recover in Jesus
name. Oh, I I just see uh the enemy has
just been after you when your physical
body and it and it just seems like when
one thing seems to come and go, then
something else is popping up. And and I
and that the Lord wants you to know that
that is the enemy trying to distract
you, trying to bring you down. And it's
time to take a stand right now. And
tonight you're taking that stand. And by
faith receive all. I said all. I said
all of the anointing that's needed to
heal every aspect, every every symptom
in the name of Jesus. I rebuke that in
her body in Jesus name. Back you
function properly. Pain you leave in the
name of Jesus. From the top of her head
to the soles of her feet. And devil you
take your hand off of God's property
[music] right now. You take your hands
off of her. She's a child of the most
high God. She's the temple of the Holy
Spirit. And the same spirit in her is
the spirit that kicks your tail all over
this earth. That spirit is rising up on
the inside of her. Oh, thank you, Lord,
that she becomes a dangerous person for
the enemy to try to attack. A dangerous
person that the enemy says, "You better
leave." No, leave that one alone cuz
she's dangerous.
Oh, she's going to she's going to come
after us. She's going to be saying
things about us. How she's been healed,
how she's been delivered, how she no
longer deals with those things any
longer because by Jesus stripes, she was
healed. Thank you, Lord, for it. Thank
you for that anointing right now. It's
flowing in your body right now. I can
feel my fingers tingling right now. The
anointing is coming in. Oh, it's healing
everything. Everything that's out of
alignment in her body. Things on the
inside. Oh, things on the inside are
being healed right now in the name of
Jesus.
You don't have to be guilty about
anything. You don't have to say, "Oh, I
ate this, so I going to have to have
that." Absolutely not. You don't have to
have any of that junk.
You don't have to [music] accept any of
that curse because you are redeemed from
it in Jesus name. Thank you father.
Thank you Lord.
>> Yes.
Yes.
Yeah.
>> Thank you Lord.
Well, you know, there was a time when
Jesus healed people that weren't
present. Actually, there was multiple
times where he did that with a centurion
servant. He said, "I'll come heal your
servant." And what did what did the
centurion say? He said, "You don't have
to come. Just speak the word. Just speak
the word." We're going to speak some
words tonight. We're going to speak some
words. Thank you for standing in.
Father, in the name of Jesus, we speak
to that inflammation in Caleb's mouth
right now in the name of Jesus. Thank
you, Lord. He does not have [music] to
have this. Oh, I see this as a sign in
his life. Oh, thank you, Lord, that
right now that healing power is going
into his body, mouth, you be restored in
the name of Jesus. Thank you, Lord. And
there'll be no other explanation. Oh,
no. the the the way it was done, the way
it happened, there'll be no one [music]
to get credit but God almighty. Thank
you, Lord. Thank you, Lord. We speak to
that mouth right now in Jesus name. Be
healed in Jesus name.
Oh, thank you, Father.
And he'll and I and I just see this.
He'll say he'll give glory to God
without even realizing he did it. He'll
be like, "Whoa, I didn't know I said
that." But he'll give glory to God.
It'll just come slipping out of his
mouth. Just come right out of his
spirit. He'll give glory to God for it.
Thank you, Lord. He's healed by Jesus
stripes.
>> Thank you, Lord.
>> Thank you, Jesus, for that anointing
flowing in his mouth right now in Jesus
name. Restoring in Jesus name. Thank
you, Lord. And here's something else I
heard the Lord say. You know, everybody
that Jesus healed in the in all of his
ministry, you know, they weren't perfect
people. None of them were even born
again.
Let me tell you something. Nothing
disqualifies you. Nothing.
Nothing disqualifies.
Thank you, Lord. Praise you, Father.
Thank you, Lord.
Pain gone.
Pain from that kidney stone. Yeah. Yep.
Father, in the name of Jesus, as we lay
hands on her, we do exactly what you
said. The anointing oil right now is
flowing in her body. Thank you, Lord.
Thank you, Lord. Pain you leave right
now in Jesus name. Oh, kidney stone,
you're rebuked in her body. Anything
remaining, anything trying to form, I
rebuke it in the name of Jesus. We come
into agreement with Crystal right now. I
thank you, Lord, that that anointing is
flowing in her body right now. Healing
what has been damaged. Oh, restoring
what's been damaged in the name of
Jesus. Oh, this is nothing but a silly
little distraction. Just a silly little
distraction. And in the name of Jesus,
we call this finished, done, over in the
name of Jesus. Thank you, Lord, for that
anointing. Thank you right now. Right
now, in the name of Jesus.
The spirit of the Lord is upon you. He's
anointed you. And that anointing removes
burdens. This is a burden. This is a
burden. I rebuke that in Jesus name. I
rebuke [music] that burden. Tell it to
leave and anointing. You do what you do.
Set her free in Jesus name. Thank you,
Lord. Yes, ma'am.
Let's pray for you. Okay, we lay hands
on you and pray for you. Thank you,
Father.
Oh, for the childlike faith. Oh, you
said in your word, you said, "Oh, keep
them away. Keep them away." And no,
Jesus, you said, "Bring them in. Bring
them in." Thank you Lord for that
healing power. Thank you Lord for
removing that itch in the name of Jesus.
Restoring her skin, restoring her body.
Oh, I thank you Lord for that anointing
right now in the name of Jesus. Even at
her age, she's experiencing it. This is
the normal. This is normal. This is just
the norm. Thank you, Father, for that
anointing removing this itch in Jesus
name. And we just speak wholeness over
her body in the name of Jesus. This will
not be a lingering thing. This thing
ends [music] tonight in the name of
Jesus. Thank you Lord for the anointing.
The elders have laid hands on anointed
her with the oil of the Holy Spirit and
body. You recover in Jesus name. We
speak to it. Say recover in the name of
Jesus. Amen. Amen. Thank you Lord.
Praise you father.
busted your hand.
>> Oh man.
>> Yes.
>> Father, in the name of Jesus, we thank
you for that anointing.
You said you said that Josh could come
forward tonight and call on prayer. The
prayer of faith you said will save the
sick. We are to anoint him with oil
right now. The oil is flowing in his arm
right now in his hand. Oh, restoring
what's been messed up. Oh, the nerves
and the tendons. Oh, anything out of
alignment. Anything that's off, anything
that's broken, we speak restoration over
it right now [music] in the name of
Jesus.
Thank you for the anointing.
Thank you for that anointing flowing in
his hand right now. The power is flowing
right now. Oh, it's flowing right now in
the name of Jesus.
things that he couldn't do now he'll be
able to do. Thank you Lord. We call his
hand restored in the name of Jesus.
>> Restoration,
wholeness,
>> healing in the name.
>> In the name of Jesus. Thank you Lord.
Thank you Lord.
>> Were you able to bend it before?
>> Praise God. Thank you Lord.
>> Well that seems to be working.
Praise God. Thank you, Lord.
>> Thank you, Jesus.
>> Thank you, Lord. Praise. Let's just
praise him for a minute. Let's just
praise him for a minute. Thank you,
Lord. Thank you, Lord. Jesus, for being
our healer. Thank you, Lord. Pastor
Chris is not the healer. Jesus is the
healer.
But Jesus has anointed us. He's
empowered us to lay hands on broken
hands,
broken bodies, sickness, and disease.
And sickness, disease, and broken hands
have to bow their knee to the anointing
of the Holy One of Israel, Jesus Christ,
the anointed one. Thank you, Father.
Thank you, Jesus. I'm stirred up. Thank
you, Lord. Praise God. Did you need
prayer?
Oh, his tongue. Yeah, he told me earlier
he bit his tongue earlier. [music]
Father, in the name of Jesus. Oh, thank
you, Father, for restoring his tongue.
Oh, that pain that Oh, we we've all
experienced it. Every single one of us
have experienced pain. We we bite our
tongue. And so, I thank you, Lord, for
restoration in his tongue in Jesus name.
I rebuke the pain right now in the name
of Jesus. The spirit of the Lord is upon
us. You have anointed us and that
anointing is flowing in his body right
now in the name of Jesus. We thank you
for it. We praise you for it in Jesus
name. Amen. Amen. Thank you Lord. How's
your tongue feeling?
You feeling better too? Praise God.
Thank you Lord.
>> Yes ma'am.
>> Your leg. Which leg is it?
Well, let me just get down here and
we're just going to lay hands on your
leg. And when we lay hands on your leg,
the power of God is [music] going to
come into your leg. Okay? Father, in the
name of Jesus, we rebuke this pain in
Jesus name. Thank you, Lord. Her leg is
restored. Whatever the source of this
pain is, we don't even have to know what
it is. It could just be a bruise. It
just could be something else. Doesn't
matter. Leg be restored in the name of
Jesus. The spirit of the Lord is upon
us. You have anointed us.
>> That anointing right now is flowing in
her leg in Jesus name. Restoring and
removing the pain. Pain you be gone in
Jesus name. You leave her body in the
name of Jesus. Thank you Lord. Praise
you. Now you can run and jump and play.
Thank you Lord. Praise God.
>> His tummy.
>> Okay. Well, let's pray for his tummy.
Father, in the name of Jesus,
we do exactly what you said in your
word. You said the spirit of the Lord is
upon us. You've anointed us. Thank you,
Lord, for that anointing. Thank you,
Lord. That anointing right now is
healing his tummy in Jesus name. Tummy,
you line up. You function properly in
the name of Jesus. That anointing right
now is healing his stomach. Stomach
ache, you leave his body, you don't
belong there. You leave. He's a child of
the most high God. You have no right to
him in the name of Jesus. And we rebuke
this attack on his body [music] in Jesus
name. Amen. Amen. Thank you Lord. Praise
God. Thank you Lord. Thank you Lord. Who
wants to stand in for Jada? Kim, you
look like Jada.
You're here in front of me. Jada was
having some health issues. Jamie and
Jasmine's little girl's having some
health issues this morning. And so she
had to go uh to the to the ER actually
this morning. And so uh I just want you
to stand in for her because you know
what? The anointing has no distance
limitations.
There are no distance in the spirit. So,
Father, in the name of Jesus, as I lay
my head right now on Tim's head, thank
you, Lord, that that anointing is
flowing in Jada's body in the name of
Jesus. Oh, we speak to her brain.
>> You align in Jesus name. Things that are
off, you come back into balance in the
name of Jesus. We will not have this. We
will not stand for it. We won't Oh no.
Oh no. Well, this is not happening in
her body. Oh, no. The the doctors have
said, "Well, that's the way it's going
to be because it's hereditary." But the
Lord says it's not.
>> The Lord says it's not hereditary.
She's a child of the most high.
And that anointing right now is
correcting
everything that's out of alignment in
the name of Jesus. Thank you, Lord.
Thank you for the anointing. The spirit
of the Lord is upon us. You've anointed
us. Thank you, Lord, for complete and
total restoration in the name of Jesus.
Amen. And amen. Thank you, Lord. Praise
you, Father. Yes, ma'am. Yes,
Jimmy.
>> Yes.
>> Thank you, Lord.
>> Yes. Absolutely.
She's standing in for her friend Jimmy
that's got heart issues in the name of
Jesus as we lay hands on Francesca
tonight. Oh, thank you Lord that hands
are being laid right now on Jimmy. Oh,
thank you Lord. You're the restorer. The
anointing restores. Thank you Lord for
restoration in Jimmy's heart in Jesus
name. Thank put your hand right there on
on where her heart is. Thank you Lord
for restoration right now in the name of
Jesus heart. We're speaking to you
heart, you beat properly in Jesus name.
Heart, you be restored in the name of
Jesus Christ of Nazareth. The anointing
is now touching you. The anointing is
repairing you. The anointing is causing
you to be properly. You line up in the
name of Jesus. Thank you, Lord, for it.
We call it done in the name of Jesus.
>> The spirit of the Lord is upon us. You
have anointed us. to do this to heal
hearts that are not working [music]
properly. Broken hearts, but not just in
in emotional broken hearts, but physical
hearts that are broken. I thank you,
Lord. His heart is restored.
He gets a new heart. Oh, thank you,
Lord. It's like new. And the doctors
will even say, "It's like you got a new
heart. It looks like the old one, but
you got a new one." And it's because of
the anointing. Thank you, Lord, for that
anointing. restoring. Oh, and everything
that's been damaged because of his
heart. Oh, any artery, any vein, any any
uh limb, any other symptoms that he's
having, I rebuke those in the name of
Jesus. Thank you for that anointing from
the top of his head to the soles of his
feet right now. Restoring, restoring,
restoring what the doctors say cannot be
restored that they say, "Oh, he'll have
this problem the rest of his life." We
say no because of the anointing.
It's restoring right now in Jesus name.
Thank you Lord for it. Praise you for
Thank you Lord. You you you talk to him.
You tell him what we just prayed
tonight.
>> Thank you Lord. Praise you father. That
anointing is working in his body in the
name of Jesus. Praise you father. Let's
just thank you for a moment. Isn't God
good? Let's just thank him for a moment.
Thank you Lord for the anointing.
[music]
Let's pray in the spirit because the
spirit of the Lord is upon us. Let's
just pray in the spirit.
Let's just sing in the spirit. Sing in
the spirit tonight.
Thank you, Lord.
>> [music and singing]
>> Let's just keep singing. Just keep
singing for a moment.
[music]
[singing]
>> [singing and music]
>> Owen, is it okay if I pray for you?
>> Come up. I want to lay hands on you and
pray for you. Thank you, Lord.
>> I just felt impressed to pray for you. I
don't know what I'm praying over, but
the spirit knows. Praise the Lord. Thank
you, Lord. Is there something or no?
Don't even tell me. Thank you, Lord.
Father, in the name of Jesus, I pray for
my brother right now. Oh, the spirit of
the Lord is upon us. You've anointed us.
He's anointed. Thank you for that
anointing that's on his life. Thank you,
Father. Thank you, Lord, that he's
protected and he's kept in Jesus name.
Oh, thank you, Lord. We rebuke any
attack from the enemy that would try to
come after him
and convince him and change his mind
about things. No, no, no.
The Lord says no.
Thank you, Lord. You're a child of the
most high. You don't have to accept
anything less than what God says you
are. What God says you can have.
Thank you, Lord. And I just feel in my
spirit that there have been some things
that have been said about you, been
spoken either to you or about you that
have kind of put some limits in your
life. And the Lord wanted me to tell you
tonight, those limits don't exist.
Those don't exist. Those limits are
self-imposed limits.
Thank you, Lord. There are no limits.
From God's perspective, there are no
limits to what you can do.
He said you can do all things through
Christ, through the anointing that's on
your life, strengthening you, empowering
you. You have value. You have purpose.
Thank you, Lord. The enemy has has tried
to kind of work on you a little bit.
Say, well, you know, you're not much of
[music] this or not much of that. And
he's really tried to belittle you a
little bit. tried to say, "Well, you're
not this, you're not this kind of
person." And and you know, the Lord
would say, "Stop listening to that voice
and stop playing the comparison game.
He's anointed you in a unique and
special way." We're all unique and
special.
And don't let the devil lie to you.
Don't let the devil persuade you and and
try to tell you that you're not enough
and that you can't. The Lord says you
can. You can what? You can do all things
through Christ strengthening you.
Whatever it is he puts on your heart to
do. Whatever it is you stretch forth
your hand to do, the Lord says he'll
make you prosper. You step out in faith,
you follow the leading of the Holy
Spirit and you do what he tells you to
do and the Lord said I'm when my hand is
in it and you're following me, it'll
prosper and you'll be successful in all
that you do.
Be bold. Be courageous in the name of
Jesus. Thank you Lord. Thank you Lord
for boldness in Jesus name. Thank you
Father. Does that bear witness with your
spirit? Thank you Lord. Praise you
father. Thank you Lord. Let's just pray
in the spirit [music] for a minute. It's
okay. It's Wednesday night. We might as
well hang out a while. Thank you Lord.
Thank you Lord. [singing]
depression.
>> You're suffering from depression
tonight. I want you to come forward
right now. [music and singing]
>> You're suffering from depression. You've
been depressed.
Somebody here has been depressed. You've
been suffering from it. It may maybe
it's been a short-term thing. I don't
know if it's short or long term, but
you've been suffering from depression.
The Lord says healing [music] night is
not just for physical things.
Healing not is for everything that's
been hindering you. Thank you, Lord.
Thank you, Lord.
I heard the Lord say this. You may not
think it's been depression, but you've
had thoughts that have been belittling,
be degrading thoughts, and you've been
thinking about bad things. And like,
it's like these bad things have been
rehearsing in your mind. And the Lord
said, "That's the seed of depression,
anticipation of evil,
and you've been rehearsing these
negative things in your mind." And the
Lord said, "Yeah, you don't recognize
it's depression. That's why you're not
coming forward." But the Lord said, "The
seed is there.
The seed has been planted of
depression." And you need to deal with
that seed. You need to deal with it
tonight. It needs to be uprooted
in the name of Jesus. Thank you, Lord.
Thank you, Lord. You've had bad
thoughts, evil thoughts, just rehearsing
over and over in your mind.
Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Jesus. We'll
wait just a minute.
>> And I just heard the Lord say that. You
said, "Well, that's not me. I'm not a
depressed person." But you've been
having these thoughts.
Those negative thoughts will lead to and
grow depression in your mind.
And the Lord wants you free tonight.
That's why he had me say it. That's why
you came tonight. Didn't even know you
came for it, but that's why you came to
be set free. Thank you, Jesus.
Thank you Lord. Thank you Lord. Let's
just worship him. Let's worship him.
>> Oh [music and singing] we bless your
name. We bless your name.
[music]
[singing]
Oh [music and singing] yeah, I'm a man.
I'm a
>> Thank you. You know, it ought not be it
ought not be com uncomfortable for us to
just worship in his presence.
I think so many times we get in [music]
a hurry. We got to do this or do that.
But just spending time in his presence
listening. I want I want you to practice
that right now. Just listen. Listen to
what he's saying. You might get answers
to questions you've had your entire life
in the next two or three minutes as we
worship.
Thank you. That's what I'm doing. I'm
listening. I'm listening for more
instructions.
>> Thank you, Lord.
Just listen. Worship him and listen in
your heart. What is he telling you?
What is he saying?
He may give you a word to [music] share
with everybody. Share it.
>> Thank you, Lord.
Thank you, Jesus. [singing]
Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Lord. Grab
this in the basket. Thank you, Lord.
>> I just had it in my heart that someone's
got a word. Jonathan.
>> So, uh, something I saw today bore
witness with my spirit and I believe I
should share it here today. Uh, there
was a man that Jesus approached and he
asked him a very simple question. He
said, "Do you want to be healed?"
>> Do you want to be healed?
And it it's simple in theory, but the
man had been there for years sitting
there waiting for the stirring of the
waters. And many of you guys here
tonight, I believe the Lord is asking
that question.
Do you want to be healed? Do you want to
follow me for the rest of your life? Do
you want to serve me? Do you want to
fulfill the purpose that I have for you?
>> Why is he asking you that? Because is
going to require you to get up and move
from where you are to where God is
calling you to be. Yes,
that is the vision and the purpose of
this church.
How many of you guys would would say
tonight
that you are in a position where God is
asking you to do something that may be
uncomfortable
that that may be something that requires
you to make a change that you're not
sure about yet. Remember the Bible says
count the cost. Count the cost before
you start.
There's something powerful in
consecration
and saying, "Lord, I will do whatever
you ask me to do."
>> Thank you, Lord.
>> Amen.
>> Thank you, Jesus.
>> Would that qualify to anybody here
today?
>> Thank you, Jesus. Thank you, Jesus.
>> Thank you, Jesus.
>> Come, come forward
>> if you would if that applies to you here
today.
>> Thank you, Lord.
>> Thank you, Jesus. Thank you, Lord.
>> It requires boldness
to step out to answer that question
truthfully.
>> Thank you, Lord.
>> Because it means that you're not willing
to sit there any longer.
>> Thank you, Jesus.
>> Amen.
>> Amen. And L, I want to say something
before we pray. We're anointed to do
this, by the way. The spirit of the Lord
is upon us. We're anointed. This
ministry is anointed. You know what this
ministry is anointed to do? exactly what
he just said. Move people from where
they are to where God's called them to
be. That's the word he spoke over this
church. So as we lay hands on you, that
anointing is on you. You're a part of
this church. Father, in the name. Go
ahead and pray, John.
>> Amen.
>> In the name.
>> So tonight, the Lord asks you that
question.
>> Will you choose me? Will you choose the
plan that I have for you? Will you step
out beyond where you've been? because
there's a place for you.
>> Thank you.
>> There's a place beyond [music] where
you've been that he wants for you. So
say yes.
>> Say yes tonight. And he will cause you
to grow. He will cause you to go beyond
where you've been.
>> And you will go further than you ever
imagined.
>> The Bible says that we do not know the
plans that he has for us. the the
fullness, the wonders, the the the
greatness of it because it it requires
us to step out
>> to step out to see it one step at a
time. So I believe tonight there is an
anointing on you that there is a grace
on you
>> to step out and go beyond where you've
been before in Jesus name.
>> In the name of Jesus.
>> Amen.
>> Amen. Amen. Thank you Lord. Praise you
father. Thank you Lord. Praise you,
Father. Kaylee, can we pray for you?
Thank you, Lord.
I just felt impressed. Is it okay if we
just do this, guys? Is it okay if we
just just are led by the spirit for just
a moment? It's okay if you say, "No, I'm
going to do it anyway." So, praise God.
I just Good practice. I don't know. The
Lord just want me to
pray over you. Thank you, Lord. Father,
in the name of Jesus.
Oh, this is what I hear the Lord saying
right now. The spirit of the Lord is
upon you because he's anointed you.
He's anointed you in ways
that you haven't thought you were. He's
anointed you in aspects in in uh
abilities
that that you thought weren't in you
that you thought you didn't have. But
the Lord is saying, "Hey, I put those
things there." And those things that
you've seen in your heart already that
you've seen yourself doing and you
thought, "Oh, no. I'm no that." No, no.
Those things that you've seen you doing
and And I sure hear the Lord saying this
too. Your family doing your family
doing. This is not just a Kaye thing.
This is a family thing. Thank you, Lord.
Oh, he's working in your family right
now in the name of Jesus. Thank you,
Lord. This is a family anointing. The
family will be ministering together. The
family will Thank you, Lord.
We pray over their entire Let's pray
over their whole family. Your whole
family right now in the name of Jesus.
Oh, for Kevin, for cash. Thank you,
Lord, for Thank you, Lord. Oh, yes.
Thank you, Jesus. In the name of Jesus.
We thank you, Lord, over every one of
them. Thank you, Lord, for Colby. In the
name of Jesus, the anointing is on her
as well. Thank you, Jesus.
Thank you, Father.
Thank you, Lord. To do what you've
called them to do.
Oh, it's a season right now that you're
in, but the Lord says seasons change.
Seasons change. You're not going to be
in this season forever. Seasons change.
He's already working. He's already
moving. And you don't you don't you're
not going to see it all in the natural.
You're not going to see things change
overnight, just [music] like the
changing of seasons don't just change
overnight. But gradually, you'll see the
season beginning to change. Just like in
the spring, you start to see flowers
starting to bloom, trees starting to
bloom, and you'll be like, "Wow, it's a
little cool outside, but look at that.
Look at that. Things [music] are
beginning to change. You'll see the same
thing in your family. You'll begin to
see the same thing. Oh, thank you, Lord.
Things are changing. The anointing The
anointing is on. The anointing is on
your family because God doesn't just
call individuals, he calls families.
Thank you, Lord, for that anointing on
our life in the name of Jesus. Praise
you, Father. Thank you, Lord. Let's give
the Lord a hand for that one. Thank you,
Jesus. Thank you, Father.
Thank you, Lord. We serve a good God.
Amen. Thank you, Lord.
Let's just pray for a minute. Thank you
Lord. Thank you Jesus.
>> Thank you Lord.
>> Thank you Jesus.
>> Thank you Lord. To say that I had dental
work done today and it's been hurting
pretty much ever since. [music] And then
when we were praying even coming up here
it just kept hurting and kept hurting
and just in the midst of praying he's
[music] completely gone. So I don't have
any more pain. So I'm very thankful for
that. So
>> thank you
>> just being in the anointing.
>> Amen. See, you can minister under the
anointing when you're having physical
pain yourself. Well, that's a good word
for somebody. That's a good word for
somebody. Some of y'all disqualified
yourself because of your condition. Or
you said, "No, I experienced this and I
have this problem, so I can't minister
to nobody." That's a lie from the pit of
hell. That same anointing in you will
heal your body and flow into somebody
else and heal their body. Thank you,
Jesus, for it. Thank you, Lord, for
healing teeth, toothaches in the name of
Jesus. Thank you, Lord.
Thank you, Lord. Oh, you're such a good
father. You're such a good father. Thank
you, Jesus.
Thank you, Lord.
>> Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Jesus.
Chains
broken [singing and music]
hearts
open
you [singing]
are healed in Jesus
name.
>> Chains be [singing and music] broken
hearts be open.
You [singing] are healed in Jesus
name.
Chains be broken, [singing]
hearts [music] be open.
You are healed in Jesus [singing]
name.
Hearts be [singing]
eyes be.
>> Thank you Jesus
name. [singing]
>> Thank you Lord. I want everybody to say
this with me. The spirit of the Lord
>> The Spirit of the Lord
>> is upon me.
>> You've anointed me.
>> You've anointed me
>> to preach the gospel
>> preach the gospel
>> to the poor.
>> You've anointed me
>> to lay hands
>> on blind eyes
>> on blind eyes.
>> You've anointed me
>> to cast out demons
>> to cast out [music] demons
>> in the name
>> In the name
>> of Jesus. of Jesus,
>> the anointed one.
>> The anointed one
>> with his anointing
>> with his anointing.
>> Thank you, Lord. Thank you, Father.
>> Oh, thank you, Lord.
>> Thank you, Jesus.
>> I just hear the Lord saying this, too.
You need to know who you are.
If you only knew who you were and whose
you were,
renew your mind to it.
Who do you belong to? Who's anointed
you? That should drive out all fear of
failure. Drive out all fear of stepping
out in faith. God,
his anointing is on your life.
Use it.
You're anointed to go to work tomorrow.
Praise you, Father. Don't Don't dread
it. You're anointed to do it. You're
anointed to fix problems nobody [music]
else can fix. You're anointed to have
ideas out of your spirit that nobody's
thought about. We got [music] a problem.
We need a new idea. The anointing will
bring you an idea.
Thank you, Lord.
I heard the Lord saying this. The church
has not operated in this anointing as
they should. And this is just a little
sample tonight. You can operate under
this anointing all the time. The
anointing is not just for healing.
The supernatural power, this anointing
that's on your life is to do to do what?
Whatever is needed.
It's kind of like spiritual gifts. They
say, "Which one's the best spiritual
gift?" It's the one that's needed at the
time. You're anointed to do that one.
God's anointed you for such a time as
this. Amen. I want to pray over
everybody before we go. Father, in the
name of Jesus,
I thank you for this church. Oh, it's an
anointed church. Powerful church. Thank
you, Lord, for the anointing on every
single person's life here tonight. I
thank you, Lord, that we tonight are
coming up to a new level, functioning
in, operating with, cooperating with you
in that anointing.
And that everything that we do in this
life from this point forward, everything
that we are challenged with, every time
that we feel like we're not enough, we
feel like we can't, that's when we
connect with that anointing. That's when
the anointing takes over and we say, "I
can do all things. Not in my own
strength, not in my own ability, but
through Christ and his anointing. The
anointed one and his anointing on my
life is enabling me to go do all that
you've called me to do to be the
Christian you've called me to be in the
name of Jesus. We thank you for it. We
praise you for it in Jesus name. Praise
you, Father. I don't like to close
services like this. I just like to keep
going. Amen. Praise God. Thank you,
Lord. Isn't God good? Amen. He's a good
father. Invite someone to church this
Sunday. I know it's Mother's Day. You
have something else to say,
>> Miss Francis Marie. You know, tomorrow
is her birthday. She has to come here.
[laughter]
>> If I know it's your birthday, you better
watch out.
>> Let's have an anointed song, shall we?
>> We love her. She's been a part of our
church for many [music] years and a huge
blessing. And we love you and we just
want to honor you. So, we're gonna sing
happy birthday.
>> Here we go.
Happy birthday [singing] to you.
Happy birthday to you.
>> Happy birthday,
Princess Marie.
[laughter]
>> Happy birthday to you.
>> All right. Thank you guys. You guys are
dismissed. God bless y'all.
Hey, we [music] also need to get the
sanctuary ready for school tomorrow. So,
if you have time to help with the
chairs, that would be awesome.
over.
We sing hallelu.
We sing hallelu. [singing and music]
The lamb is over.
We sing hallelu.
We sing [singing] hallelu.
We sing [music] hallelu.